=A Taste of First Love=
= طعم الحب الأول =
=Episode 12=
= الحلقة 12 =
I missed you very much.
اشتقت اليك كثيرا
Don't leave me.
لا تتركنى.
Stay here with me.
ابق هنا معي.
Da Bai, stop that. Sit down.
دا باي ، توقف عن ذلك.  اجلس.
Da Bai?
دا باي؟
Isn't it the dog from a few years back?
أليس هو الكلب منذ بضع سنوات مضت؟
Dai,
داي ،
how many times should I repeat?
كم مرة يجب أن أكرر؟
Now, tell me
الآن أخبرني
who's the boss here?
من هو الرئيس هنا؟
List down
أسفل القائمة
all our clients
جميع عملائنا
and send it over again.
وأرسلها مرة أخرى.
You need time?
تحتاج وقت؟
You have never done that before this?
لم تفعل ذلك من قبل؟
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
I just want to stand up.
أنا فقط أريد أن أقف.
Check all the tags
تحقق من جميع العلامات
of Huarong's products
من منتجات Huarong ل
and send me a summary of them.
وأرسل لي ملخصًا عنها.
But there are so many of them.
لكن هناك الكثير منهم.
I need it.
أنا في حاجة إليه.
Okay.
تمام.
Whatever you say.
أيا كان ما تقوله.
Mr. Bai,
السيد باي ،
here's the summary report.
ها هو تقرير الملخص.
If there's nothing else,
إذا لم يكن هناك شيء آخر ،
I'll leave first.
سأغادر أولا.
Do you really hate to spend time with me?
هل حقا تكره قضاء الوقت معي؟
I'm so sad.
انا حزين جدا.
You were the one who wouldn't let go of me
كنت الشخص الذي لن يتركني
and said we should sleep together last night.
وقال يجب أن ننام معًا الليلة الماضية.
I was drunk.
كنت ثملا.
If I behaved weirdly,
إذا تصرفت بغرابة ،
please don't take it seriously.
من فضلك لا تأخذ الأمر على محمل الجد.
Boss, are you there?
بوس ، هل أنت هناك؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Without my permission,
دون إذن مني،
no one will ever come in.
لن يأتي أحد أبدًا.
Don't you have any feelings towards me?
أليس لديك أي مشاعر تجاهي؟
If I wasn't the one
إذا لم أكن أنا
who sent you home last night,
من أرسلك إلى المنزل الليلة الماضية ،
would you allow others to do so?
هل تسمح للآخرين بفعل ذلك؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
That means you're falling in love with me too.
هذا يعني أنك تقع في حبي أيضًا.
Stop flattering yourself.
توقف عن الإطراء على نفسك.
I don't remember anything about last night.
لا أتذكر أي شيء عن الليلة الماضية.
But there were only the two of us
لكن لم يكن هناك سوى اثنين منا
and you ran into my arms.
وركضت في ذراعي.
Isn't that an obvious sign?
أليست هذه علامة واضحة؟
I'll come in now, Boss.
سآتي الآن ، بوس.
What did I say about never coming in
ماذا قلت عن عدم الحضور
without my permission?
دون إذن مني؟
I'm sorry, Boss.
أنا آسف يا رئيس.
This door isn't functioning well.
هذا الباب لا يعمل بشكل جيد.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Boss,
رئيس،
the handover between Chicheng Group and us
التسليم بين مجموعة تشيتشنغ وبيننا
is going smoothly.
يسير بسلاسة.
Boss?
رئيس؟
All right,
حسنا،
just follow the procedures.
فقط اتبع الإجراءات.
Okay.
تمام.
Come out.
يظهر.
My hair!
شعري!
You...
أنت...
Unbutton it.
قم بفك الزر.
Boss,
رئيس،
I forgot to take the document.
لقد نسيت أن آخذ الوثيقة.
I didn't see anything.
لم ارى شيئا.
Bai Zeliu,
باي زيليو ،
you did it on purpose!
فعلت ذلك عن قصد!
I did it on purpose?
فعلت ذلك عمدا؟
This is to my disadvantage, don't you see?
هذا ليس في مصلحتي ، ألا ترى؟
How could I do it on purpose?
كيف يمكنني أن أفعل ذلك عن قصد؟
But I don't want people commenting about us.
لكني لا أريد أن يعلق الناس عنا.
There's nothing to hide about our relationship.
لا يوجد شيء نخفيه في علاقتنا.
Who cares about them?
من يهتم بهم؟
How about I issue a memo,
ماذا لو أصدرت مذكرة ،
saying whoever stands in the way of our relationship,
يقول كل من يقف في طريق علاقتنا ،
their salaries will be deducted.
سيتم خصم رواتبهم.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Are you out of your mind?
هل جننت؟
I don't want anyone to affect our relationship.
لا أريد أن يؤثر أحد على علاقتنا.